Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1, Section 4: Boxes 67-88
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1, Section 4: Boxes 67-88
- Box: 85, Folder: 2 (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Item 50: Big Labor and Big Strikes: Analysis and Recommendations, Publication (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Item 51: Action reports, Publication (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Item 52: Special Bibliography of NAM Industrial Relations Publications, Publication (Box 85, Folder 2)
- Box: 85, Folder: 3 (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: A Problem For Every Citizen: Monopoly Power as Exercised by Labor Unions, Publication (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Effective Communication In Industry, Publication (Box 85, Folder 3)
    By Paul Pigors. Lt. Rush Toland Memorial Study No. 1. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: People vs. Rabbits, Publication (Box 85, Folder 3)
    By NAM (National Association of Manufacturers). July 3, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Toward Steadier Work and Pay: Industrial Management Uses Practical Techniques To Provide Greater Job Security, Publication (Box 85, Folder 3)
    By NAM (National Association of Manufacturers). August 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Peacetime Plans of Industrial Companies, Publication (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: The Effect of The War On Income, Wages, And Living Costs, Publication (Box 85, Folder 3)
    By NAM (National Association of Manufacturers). October 1943. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Women in postwar industry, Publication (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: Management's Views At The Labor-Management Conference, Publication (Box 85, Folder 3)
    By Ira Mosher; Eric Johnston; H. W. Prentis, Jr. November 5-6, 1945. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Toward Steadier Work and Pay: Industrial Management Uses Practical Techniques To Provide Greater Job Security, Publication (Box 85, Folder 3)
    By NAM (National Association of Manufacturers). August 1955. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Wages, Prices, Profits, and Inflation, Publication (Box 85, Folder 3)
    By NAM (National Association of Manufacturers). September 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Collective Bargaining: A Management Guide, Publication (Box 85, Folder 3)
    By NAM (National Association of Manufacturers). July 1943. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Do The Seniority Rights of Employees Survive An Expired Contract?, Publication (Box 85, Folder 3)
    By Eugene A. Hoffman. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Do The Seniority Rights of Employees Survive An Expired Contract?, Publication (Box 85, Folder 3)
    By Eugene A. Hoffman. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Your Opportunities In Science and Engineering, Publication (Box 85, Folder 3)
    By NAM (National Association of Manufacturers). September 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Better Communications mean Better Teamwork: A Check List for analysis of the Company's progress in developing understanding with Employees, Publication (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Item 16: Human Relations And Efficient Production, Publication (Box 85, Folder 3)
    By NAM (National Association of Manufacturers). Revised February, 1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: The Public and Industrial Peace: A National Labor Policy to Minimize Industrial Strikes, Publication (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Item 18: The Public and Industrial Peace: A National Labor Policy to Minimize Industrial Strikes, Publication (Box 85, Folder 3)
    By NAM (National Association of Manufacturers). Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: The Public And Industrial Peace: A National Labor Policy to Minimize Industrial Industrial Strikes, Publication (Box 85, Folder 3)
    By NAM (National Association of Manufacturers). Copy 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: The Public and Industrial Peace: A National Labor Policy to Minimize Industrial Strikes, Publication (Box 85, Folder 3)
    By NAM (National Association of Manufacturers). Copy 4. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Questions and Answers About Postwar Problems: As developed in panel discussions at NAM postwar conferences, Publication (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Item 22: The Public and Industrial Peace: A National Labor Policy to Minimize Industrial Strikes, Publication (Box 85, Folder 3)
    By NAM (National Association of Manufacturers). Copy 5. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: The Issue of the Shorter Work Week, Publication (Box 85, Folder 3)
    By NAM (National Association of Manufacturers). February 1961. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Profit and Loss In The Enterprise System, Publication (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Item 25: Industry's View On Postwar Problems: An Extract from the Second Report of the Postwar Committee, Publication (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Item 26: The Ties That Bind: Findings And Concepts About People And Organizations, Publication (Box 85, Folder 3)
    By John Paul Jones. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Report on employment of Mature Workers, Publication (Box 85, Folder 3)
    By NAM (National Association of Manufacturers). September, 1960. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Automation: A Background Memorandum, Publication (Box 85, Folder 3)
    By Edward I. Maher. April 1960. Item is in English.
  - Item 29: Human Relations and Efficient Production, Publication (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Item 30: Calling All Jobs: an introduction to the automatic machine age, Publication (Box 85, Folder 3)
    By NAM (National Association of Manufacturers). November 1954. Item is in English.
  - Item 31: Calling All Jobs: an introduction to the automatic machine age, Publication (Box 85, Folder 3)
    By NAM (National Association of Manufacturers). November 1954. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 32: Calling All Jobs: an introduction to the automatic machine age, Publication (Box 85, Folder 3)
    By NAM (National Association of Manufacturers). November 1954. Copy 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 33: Human Relations and Efficient Production, Publication (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Item 34: Satisfying the Salaried Employee, Publication (Box 85, Folder 3)
    By NAM (National Association of Manufacturers). April 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 35: What Are The Facts?: An Analysis of Wage, Price and Profit Studies, Publication (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Item 36: Why Employment Relations?: A discussion of employment relations and their significance in a period of national emergency, Publication (Box 85, Folder 3)
    By Thomas Roy Jones. March 1941. Item is in English.
  - Item 37: The Nathan Report: An Appraisal of Robert R. Nathan's "A National Wage Policy for 1947", Publication (Box 85, Folder 3)
    By Research Department, National Association of Manufacturers. December 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 38: Spotlight on Union Activates: Their Impact on Individuals, The Economy and The Public, Publication (Box 85, Folder 3)
    By NAM (National Association of Manufacturers). January 1958. Item is in English.
- Box: 85, Folder: 4 (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Loopholes in the Labor Laws, Publication (Box 85, Folder 4)
    By NAM (National Association of Manufacturers). May, 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: If I Were, Publication (Box 85, Folder 4)
    By William Green; H. W. Prentis, jr. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Three's A Crowd, Publication (Box 85, Folder 4)
    By H. C. Lumb. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Men Against Time, Publication (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Second Report of the Postwar Committee of the National Association of Manufacturers, Publication (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: The Coming Crisis In Labor Law, Publication (Box 85, Folder 4)
    By Carroll E. French. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Compulsory Arbitration and Government Intervention In Labor Disputes, Publication (Box 85, Folder 4)
    By Herbert R. Northrup. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Key to Progress, Publication (Box 85, Folder 4)
    By NAM (National Association of Manufacturers). Economics-In-Action Series. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: How Do People Grow In A Business Organization?, Publication (Box 85, Folder 4)
    By Moorhead Wright. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Public and Employe Attitudes on Labor Problems, Publication (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Item 11: Check Points for Sound Collective Bargaining, Publication (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Item 12: New Frontiers, Publication (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Item 13: May the Best Man Win!, Publication (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Item 14: The Disadvantages of Labor Unionism, Publication (Box 85, Folder 4)
    By John Kirby Jr. NAM Pamphlet no.2. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Improving Attitudes Through Management Leadership, Publication (Box 85, Folder 4)
    By James N. Farr. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: A Better America: Industry's Program, Publication (Box 85, Folder 4)
    By Frederick C. Crawford; H. W. Prentis, jr.; Walter B. Weisenburger. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: The Public Be Served, Publication (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Item 18: Public Policy, Private Enterprise and the Reduction of Proverty, Publication (Box 85, Folder 4)
    By Norton E. Long. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Public Policy, Private Enterprise and the Reduction of Proverty, Publication (Box 85, Folder 4)
    By Norton E. Long. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Facts and Fancies About Automation, Publication (Box 85, Folder 4)
    By Patrick M. Boarman. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Dollars In Shirtsleeves, Publication (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Item 22: Employee Communications for Better Understanding, Publication (Box 85, Folder 4)
    By NAM (National Association of Manufacturers). Revised 1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Why and How The Wagner Act Should be Amended, Publication (Box 85, Folder 4)
    By John C. Gall. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Pioneers of Progress, Publication (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Item 25: Employee Understanding and Teamwork for Greater Productivity, Publication (Box 85, Folder 4)
    By John P. Troxell. Lt. Rush Toland Memorial Study No. 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Nothing Gained, Nothing Ventured, Publication (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Item 27: Challenge to Industry, Publication (Box 85, Folder 4)
    By Walter B. Weisenburger. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: The American Triangle of Plenty, Publication (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Item 29: The American Triangle of Plenty, Publication (Box 85, Folder 4)
    By Frederick C. Crawford. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 30: Jobs in Peacetime, Publication (Box 85, Folder 4)
    By Philip Murray; Paul G. Hoffman; William Green; Frederick C. Crawford; H. L. Derby. Item is in English.
  - Item 31: 2% for Research, Publication (Box 85, Folder 4)
    By Karl T. Compton. Item is in English.
  - Item 32: Strategic Raw Materials, Publication (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Item 33: Good Industrial Relations, Publication (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Item 34: Employee Communications for Better Understanding, Publication (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Item 35: The Critical Problem of Financing Unemployment Compensation, Publication (Box 85, Folder 4)
    By NAM (National Association of Manufacturers). November, 1961. Item is in English.
  - Item 36: The Critical Problem of Financing Unemployment Compensation, Publication (Box 85, Folder 4)
    By NAM (National Association of Manufacturers). November, 1961. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 37: Competitive Enterprise Versus Planned Economy, Publication (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Item 38: Will America Grow in the 60's?, Publication (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Item 39: Readjustment to Civilian Jobs, Publication (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Item 40: What Organized Labor Expects of Management; What Management Expects of Organized Labor, Publication (Box 85, Folder 4)
    By George Meany; Charles R. Sligh, jr. Item is in English.
  - Item 41: Facts and Fancies About Automation, Publication (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Item 42: Union Power and Labor-Management Relations, Publication (Box 85, Folder 4)
    By NAM (National Association of Manufacturers). Select proceedings from 63rd Annual Congress of American Industry. Item is in English.
  - Item 43: The Changing Face of Labor-Management Relations, Publication (Box 85, Folder 4)
    By Milton C. Lightner. Before 30th NAM Institute on Industrial Relations, March 10, 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 44: Digest of the Second Annual Industrial Relations Workshop, Publication (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Item 45: Statement of Ira Mosher before House Committee on Education and Labor, Publication (Box 85, Folder 4)
    By Ira Mosher. Item is in English.
- Box: 85, Folder: 5 (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Industry Looks At Its Relations With Employees, Publication (Box 85, Folder 5)
    By Earl Bunting. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Industry Looks At Its Relations With Employees, Publication (Box 85, Folder 5)
    By Earl Bunting. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Industry Looks At Its Relations With Employees, Publication (Box 85, Folder 5)
    By Earl Bunting. Copy 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Capital Formation Under Free Enterprise, Publication (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Capital Formation Under Free Enterprise, Publication (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Your Opportunities in Industry as a Technician, Publication (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: Labor Monopoly and Its Implications to a Free Society, Publication (Box 85, Folder 5)
    By Leo Wolman. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Security Lives in the Heart, Publication (Box 85, Folder 5)
    By Wallace F. Bennett. Adapted from an address by Wallace F. Bennett. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Rehabilitation and Training for Postwar Employment, Publication (Box 85, Folder 5)
    By NAM (National Association of Manufacturers). Panel Discussion at the Second War Congress of American Industry. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Little Known Facts About America at Work, Publication (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Item 11: Little-known Facts about America at Work, Publication (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Item 12: Human Relations and National Defense, Publication (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Item 13: War Plant Employee Transportation: Booklet Number 2: Group Riding, Publication (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Item 14: War Plant Employee Transportation: Booklet Number 3: Automobile Maintenance, Publication (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Item 15: Your Opportunities in Industry as a Skilled Craftsman, Publication (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Item 16: Workers Over 40, Publication (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Item 17: Workers Over 40, Publication (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Item 18: Open Shop Bulletin No. 16, Publication (Box 85, Folder 5)
    By NAM (National Association of Manufacturers). September 29, 1926. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Employee Displacement: Minimizing its Adverse Effects, Publication (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Item 20: The Real Aims of Union Leadership, Publication (Box 85, Folder 5)
    By NAM (National Association of Manufacturers). Pink Pamphlet. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Labor Law Reform, Publication (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Item 22: The Outlook for Construction Employment in the Postwar Transition Period, Publication (Box 85, Folder 5)
    By The Postwar Committee of National Association of Manufacturers. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Jobs, Freedom, Opportunity, Publication (Box 85, Folder 5)
    By Postwar Problems Committee of the National Association of Manufacturers. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Jobs, Freedom, Opportunity, Publication (Box 85, Folder 5)
    By Postwar Problems Committee of the National Association of Manufacturers. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Labor-Management Relations: A Look Ahead, Publication (Box 85, Folder 5)
    By Charles R. Sligh, jr. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Labor Relations: Today and Tomorrow, Publication (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Item 27: Educational Aids for Schools and Colleges 1955-56, Publication (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Item 28: Educational Aids for Schools and Colleges 1955-56, Publication (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Item 29: Human Relations and Efficient Production, Publication (Box 85, Folder 5)
    By NAM (National Association of Manufacturers). Second Edition. Item is in English.
  - Item 30: Human Relations and Efficient Production, Publication (Box 85, Folder 5)
    By NAM (National Association of Manufacturers). Second Edition. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 31: Industry's Goal - Building a Better America, Publication (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Item 32: Industry's Goal - Building a Better America, Publication (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Item 33: Industry's War Production, Publication (Box 85, Folder 5)
    By NAM (National Association of Manufacturers). Foreword by William Witherow. Item is in English.
  - Item 34: Preparing for Industrial Work, Publication (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Item 35: The Public Interest and Labor Law Reform, Publication (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Item 36: Towards Wider Job Vistas for the Physically Impaired, Publication (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Item 37: Focus on industrial Relations, Publication (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Item 38: Water in Industry, Publication (Box 85, Folder 5)
    By NAM (National Association of Manufacturers). Economic Policy Division Series no.36. Item is in English.
  - Item 39: General Meeting of Industry Mayflower Hotel -- Washington DC, Publication (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Item 40: Education-Industry Relationships, Publication (Box 85, Folder 5)
    By F. Kenneth Brasted. Item is in English.
- Box: 85, Folder: 6 (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Industrial Peace A progress Report, Publication (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Employee Benefit Programs, Publication (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Management Answers to Some Union Objections on Wage Incentives, Publication (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Preparing to Negotiate, Publication (Box 85, Folder 6)
    By NAM (National Association of Manufacturers). Management Memo no.2. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Preparing to Negotiate, Publication (Box 85, Folder 6)
    By NAM (National Association of Manufacturers). Management Memo no.2. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Seniority, Publication (Box 85, Folder 6)
    By NAM (National Association of Manufacturers). Management Memo no.1. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Seniority, Publication (Box 85, Folder 6)
    By NAM (National Association of Manufacturers). Management Memo no.1. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Should Labor Be Given a Direct Share in the Management of Industry?, Publication (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Item 9: Labor Legislation Summary Analysis of the Kennedy Bill, Publication (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Item 10: Keeping Fit for A Profit, Publication (Box 85, Folder 6)
    By Victor G. Hesier. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Industry Reports on Veterans, Publication (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Item 12: Returning Veterans, Publication (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Item 13: Stastical and Economic Background to the "Marshall Plan", Publication (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Item 14: Statement of Ira Mosher, Publication (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Item 15: Can Uncle Sam Do It Better?, Publication (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Item 16: Spotlight on Union Activities, Publication (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Item 17: NAM Law Digest, Publication (Box 85, Folder 6)
    By NAM (National Association of Manufacturers). v.9:no.3 (1947:June). Item is in English.
  - Item 18: NAM Law Digest, Publication (Box 85, Folder 6)
    By NAM (National Association of Manufacturers). v.6:no.5 (1944:June). Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Labor-Management Reporting and Disclosure Act of 1959, Publication (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Item 20: Retirement Security in a Free Society, Publication (Box 85, Folder 6)
    By NAM (National Association of Manufacturers). Economic Series no.67. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Seniority, Publication (Box 85, Folder 6)
    By NAM (National Association of Manufacturers). Management Memo no.1. Copy 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: More Housing at Less Cost, Publication (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Item 23: Human Relations and Efficient Production, Publication (Box 85, Folder 6)
    By NAM (National Association of Manufacturers). Second Edition. Copy 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Report of Committee on Industrial Relations, Publication (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Item 25: The Open Shop "Conspiracy", Publication (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Item 26: A "Model Code" for Self-Governing Industries, Publication (Box 85, Folder 6)
    By A. P. Haake. Preliminary Draft. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Statesmanship in Industrial Relations, Publication (Box 85, Folder 6)
    By Lemuel R. Boulware. NAM Series on Individualism. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Arthur J. Goldberg, Secretary of Labor: The Man and His Views, Publication (Box 85, Folder 6)
- Box: 85, Folder: 7 (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: That New Labor Law, Publication (Box 85, Folder 7)
- Box: 86, Folder: 1 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The Guaranteed Annual Wage and Its Implications To a Free Economy, Publication (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 86, Folder 1)
    By NAM Industrial Relations Department. no.1 (1946:May 9). Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 86, Folder 1)
    By NAM Industrial Relations Department. no.2 (1947:Aug. 27). Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 86, Folder 1)
    By NAM Industrial Relations Department. no.4 (1946:May 24). Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 86, Folder 1)
    By NAM Industrial Relations Department. no.7 (1946:June 20). Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 86, Folder 1)
    By NAM Industrial Relations Department. no.10 (1946:Sep. 3). Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 86, Folder 1)
    By NAM Industrial Relations Department. no.11 (1946:Aug. 24). Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 86, Folder 1)
    By NAM Industrial Relations Department. no.12 (1946:Dec. 20). Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 86, Folder 1)
    By NAM Industrial Relations Department. no.13 (1947:Feb. 5). Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 86, Folder 1)
    By NAM Industrial Relations Department. no.15 (1947:Sep. 1). Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 86, Folder 1)
    By NAM Industrial Relations Department. no.16 (1947:Oct. 1). Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 86, Folder 1)
    By NAM Industrial Relations Department. no.17 (1948:Jan.). Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 86, Folder 1)
    By NAM Industrial Relations Department. no.17 (1949:June). Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Compulsory Arbitration, Publication (Box 86, Folder 1)
    By NAM (National Association of Manufacturers). January 13, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Facts About Child Labor, Publication (Box 86, Folder 1)
    By Richard H. Edmonds; Howell Cheney. Reprinted from the Manufacturers Reocrd, July 15, 1926. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Statement of The Facts In The Controversy Between The Weirton Steel Company And The NLB, Publication (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Item 17: More Housing at Less Cost, Publication (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Item 18: Digest of Discussion: Personnel Organization and Administration, Publication (Box 86, Folder 1)
    By Howard Dirks. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Labor Management Developments - Challenge to The Nation, Publication (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Item 20: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 86, Folder 1)
    By NAM Employee Relations Department. no.24 (1956:May). Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Creating More JobsNow, Publication (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Item 22: Unemployment Causes and Cures, Publication (Box 86, Folder 1)
    By NAM (National Association of Manufacturers). Economic Series no.83 (1961:Apr.). Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Industry's View on That Taft-Hartley Law, Publication (Box 86, Folder 1)